<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dont mind to grow your mind!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="day1">Gorillas can catch human colds and other illnesses.</string>
    <string name="day2">A newborn Chinese water deer is so small it can almost be held in the palm of the hand.</string>
    <string name="day3">Ostriches can run faster than horses, and the males can roar like lions.</string>
    <string name="day4">A lion in the wild usually makes no more than twenty kills a year.</string>
    <string name="day5">The female lion does ninety percent of the hunting.</string>
    <string name="day6">The only dog that doesn’t have a pink tongue is the chow.</string>
    <string name="day7">Turtles, water snakes, crocodiles, alligators, dolphins, whales, and other water going creatures will drown if kept underwater too long.</string>
    <string name="day8">On average, dogs have better eyesight than humans, although not as colorful.</string>
    <string name="day9">Deer have no gall bladders.</string>
    <string name="day10">There is an average of 50,000 spiders per acre in green areas.</string>
    <string name="day11">The bat is the only mammal that can fly.</string>
    <string name="day12">The leg bones of a bat are so thin that no bat can walk.</string>
    <string name="day13">Some male songbirds sing more than 2000 times each day.</string>
    <string name="day14">The only mammals to undergo menopause are elephants, and humpback whales.</string>
    <string name="day15">Blue-eyed lemurs are one of two (non-human) primates to have truly blue eyes.</string>
    <string name="day16">For every human in the world there are one million ants.</string>
    <string name="day17">If you lift a kangaroo’s tail off the ground it can’t hop – they use their tails for balance.</string>
    <string name="day18">If you keep a goldfish in a dark room, it will become pale!</string>
    <string name="day19">Cows can sleep standing up, but they can only dream lying down.</string>
    <string name="day20">The average fox weighs 14 pounds.</string>
    <string name="day21">Alligators can live up to 100 years.</string>
    <string name="day22">The turkey is one of the most famous birds in North America.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_select_game">Select_game</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game_option">GameOption</string>
</resources>
